{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951133206","data":{"timestamp":" 946951133206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951134270","data":{"timestamp":" 946951134269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951143518","data":{"timestamp":" 946951143517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951144586","data":{"timestamp":" 946951144586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951147571","data":{"timestamp":" 946951147571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951148607","data":{"timestamp":" 946951148607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951152195","data":{"timestamp":" 946951152194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951153238","data":{"timestamp":" 946951153238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951157867","data":{"timestamp":" 946951157867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951158914","data":{"timestamp":" 946951158914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951161887","data":{"timestamp":" 946951161887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951162921","data":{"timestamp":" 946951162920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951170075","data":{"timestamp":" 946951170075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951171126","data":{"timestamp":" 946951171125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951190000","data":{"timestamp":" 946951190000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951191033","data":{"timestamp":" 946951191032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951196186","data":{"timestamp":" 946951196186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951197220","data":{"timestamp":" 946951197220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951205235","data":{"timestamp":" 946951205234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951206315","data":{"timestamp":" 946951206315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951209908","data":{"timestamp":" 946951209908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951210968","data":{"timestamp":" 946951210968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951217411","data":{"timestamp":" 946951217411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951218456","data":{"timestamp":" 946951218456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951221149","data":{"timestamp":" 946951221148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951222188","data":{"timestamp":" 946951222188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951226498","data":{"timestamp":" 946951226497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951227535","data":{"timestamp":" 946951227535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951231285","data":{"timestamp":" 946951231285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951232334","data":{"timestamp":" 946951232333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951235716","data":{"timestamp":" 946951235716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951236784","data":{"timestamp":" 946951236783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951243609","data":{"timestamp":" 946951243609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951244684","data":{"timestamp":" 946951244683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951266063","data":{"timestamp":" 946951266062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951267154","data":{"timestamp":" 946951267153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951270306","data":{"timestamp":" 946951270306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951271365","data":{"timestamp":" 946951271364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951276781","data":{"timestamp":" 946951276781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951277839","data":{"timestamp":" 946951277839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951280599","data":{"timestamp":" 946951280598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951281634","data":{"timestamp":" 946951281633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951287936","data":{"timestamp":" 946951287935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951289003","data":{"timestamp":" 946951289003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951294569","data":{"timestamp":" 946951294569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951295620","data":{"timestamp":" 946951295620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951306464","data":{"timestamp":" 946951306463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951307547","data":{"timestamp":" 946951307546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951310963","data":{"timestamp":" 946951310961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951311183","data":{"timestamp":" 946951311182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 0a9ca4a0-343a-4c08-9c05-4e3c3d5900bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951343670","data":{"timestamp":" 946951343669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951347696","data":{"timestamp":" 946951347695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951351746","data":{"timestamp":" 946951351746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951362436","data":{"timestamp":" 946951362436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951366402","data":{"timestamp":" 946951366402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951372641","data":{"timestamp":" 946951372641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951376114","data":{"timestamp":" 946951376114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951379919","data":{"timestamp":" 946951379919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951387750","data":{"timestamp":" 946951387750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951394901","data":{"timestamp":" 946951394901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951399072","data":{"timestamp":" 946951399072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951403338","data":{"timestamp":" 946951403338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951417368","data":{"timestamp":" 946951417368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951430050","data":{"timestamp":" 946951430050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951433557","data":{"timestamp":" 946951433557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951436818","data":{"timestamp":" 946951436817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951441697","data":{"timestamp":" 946951441697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951447289","data":{"timestamp":" 946951447288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951452891","data":{"timestamp":" 946951452891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951463285","data":{"timestamp":" 946951463285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951472652","data":{"timestamp":" 946951472652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951478882","data":{"timestamp":" 946951478881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951483403","data":{"timestamp":" 946951483402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951488187","data":{"timestamp":" 946951488187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951494470","data":{"timestamp":" 946951494470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951499879","data":{"timestamp":" 946951499879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951505666","data":{"timestamp":" 946951505666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 795abf2b-87fc-4baf-ba05-24ee394d898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951520351","data":{"timestamp":" 946951520351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 03b128e0-31d9-4587-9f0c-a8ea9e7119a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951520768","data":{"timestamp":" 946951520768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 03b128e0-31d9-4587-9f0c-a8ea9e7119a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951520847","data":{"timestamp":" 946951520847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 03b128e0-31d9-4587-9f0c-a8ea9e7119a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946951529356","data":{"timestamp":" 946951529355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_045832"," gameId":" 03b128e0-31d9-4587-9f0c-a8ea9e7119a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}